Social Media By Hennah

Hennah Hussain

DIGITAL MARKETING

Tiktok
notyourbbygx

instagram socialmediabyhennah

in LinkedIn socialmediabyhennah

Ambitious digital marketing professional with experience in social media, content creation and business start ups. Pertains a Bachelor Of Arts With Honours in Business Management with Upper Second Class Honours. Excellent communication skills, determined, and a passionate business woman.

Contact

Phone 07447224029

Email socialmediabyhennah@hotmail.com

Address
30 Longster Road, Eastleigh,
Hampshire, S050 9RS

Education

Northumbria
University
London
(Present)

MSC Digital Marketing

University of Winchester (2019-2022)

BA (HONS) Business Management achieving Upper Second Class Honours: 2:1

Peter Symonds College (2017-2019) A Levels: BTEC (Level 3) Subsidiary Diploma (Distinction*), Law, Psychology

Toynbee School(2012-2017)

GCSEs: 9 A*-C/ 9-4

Experience

Social Media Manager (July 2022 -Present) Working for The Content Consultancy's client: RightsZone. Managing the social media platforms of LinkdIn and Twitter.

Planning, creating, and scheduling of posts.

Boosted social media presence and maintained brand image.

Business owner March 2021 -Present



Started business during COVID-19 period
Named my business 'Honey Mae'

which reflects the definition of goddess of

springtime and warmth.
Sourced, branded, packaged, marketed and sold honey all myself. Received a high demand of orders which resulted in the success of all my stock being sold out within the first 2 months.

Honey Mae contact





f Facebook
Honey Mae